Your final set of drills are waiting for you
in your playbook.
They are designed to help you complete
your 90 day assessment and reset.
Capturing your wins and setting your focus
for your next season.
I also ask that you complete
your final post-course assessment.
Your feedback is invaluable to us
to help us continue to make this experience powerful
for the athletes who will come after you.
I am so incredibly proud of the work you've done.
It has been my absolute honor
to be your coach on this journey.
You've stepped into the arena,
you've faced the challenges,
you've put in the reps,
you have emerged stronger,
more focused and more aligned.
You are now a member of a very special
community of athletes.
The season may be over,
but the game of life and leadership never ends.
You've done the work and you've earned this moment.
It's time to celebrate.
Welcome to the Athleader Hall of Fame.
You have everything you need.
You've got this.
Now, make it happen.